Hello friends, my name is Sachin
and today I have brought you a video for writing.
So friends, today we are going to talk
about the Health Advantage Fund of IIT Loot.
Friends, this plan used to be with the Indian farmers earlier.
When the Loot Board
purchased it for the Indian people, then this
plan has now come to IIT Loot.
Friends, this is such a unique plan.
Many advances will be available to you in it. A
lot of customization is available,
meaning you can design this plan according to your own.
You
can set its premium according to your budget. Along with this,
you get OPD coverage in this plan
and maternity coverage too, which starts only
after the ninth. So
friends, this is a very
unique line, so friends, let's start with this plan.
First of all, friends, let's talk about the essence of this bank.
Friends, this plan comes in two variants. In
this,
you can choose from Rs 5 lakh to Rs 50 lakh.
Here you can choose from Rs 10 lakh.
15 to 20 lakhs and
you can use it according to your short term. The second
plan comes friends, in this you can use
SMS from Rs 75 lakh to ₹30000000.
Friends, there is another plan called
Prime Land, in which there is a time limit of
Rs 3 lakh to Rs 2 lakh,
but the company is not promoting it. The
company has stopped the airplane, so you should
understand that in this, friends and
family are now labeled. Talking about prevent post
reaction, friends, there are
direct links or available. Priya
Hospitalization friends, it happens when you were
not admitted in the hospital and
you had consulted a doctor, you had done
some medical tests on his fees
or you had taken some medicines, then the
expenses incurred for seven days before getting admitted in the hospital and in the same way, the
answer is just that you have returned to your home
and the doctor has later prescribed some tests for you
or has done your medical checkup or has given
you some medicines, then  These are quick
expenses, they are called post-relation
expenses. So here friends,
they are available for seven days and 90 days.
Talking about the room rent limit, friends, there is
no room rent limit here.
You
can see any room here according to your suitability.
Talking about treatment, friends, there
are such procedures here by paying 586, in which
you do not need 24-hour monitoring. If
you get admitted in the morning or get
discharged in the evening and return home,
you will still get the treatment.
Mostly, what happens in these procedures is some
surgeries like you have cataract
surgery, sinus surgery, kidney
stone surgery, so there are 586 procedures of this type.
If you
read the policy details here, you will get the complete list,
which I will give you the
link in the description, you can download it from there.
Friends, let us talk about the
death bonus, which is the
guaranteed time here, which is very low in the market.
I have included it in this.  I have seen this guaranteed, here
20% is a dominated bonus, which means
that whether you get a claim or not, your policy will
increase by 20%. Suppose you have
taken a plan of Rs 10 lakh, even if it was not claimed in that year,
Rs 2 lakh will definitely be added to your policy in the next year, that is,
next year your policy will become Rs 12 lakh.
Similarly, when you go to the fifth year,
your policy of Rs 10 lakh will become Rs
20 lakh, whether there was a problem or
not, it does not matter, you will get the
20% no claim bonus, sorry, the
guaranteed bonus of 20 percent.
Talking about the restore benefit, friends, this
also makes it quite unique
because here you get 100 percent
restoration, which
means if you have a policy of Rs 10 lakh, in any way
your Rs 10 lakh cost is incurred, then
you are given Rs 10 lakh again and it is
not necessary that it is the first exam, let's say
your first  If the claim is
of Rs 1 lakh then only it will be activated, that is,
that year you have
Rs 9 lakh from the base and Rs 10 lakh which is your
restore activated, that is a total of Rs 19 lakh will be
available to you, suppose
your second claim is of around Rs 15 lakh, Rs 17
lakh or even Rs 19 lakh, even then
you will get the benefit.
Talking about this treatment, friends, here
like Siddha Unani Homeopathy, all such
treatments in AYUSH,
you are given their benefits during cross demonstration here.
Moving ahead, friends, let's talk about the
entry age limit, friends, here
any healthy person from 18 years to 65 years
can easily buy this plan. If we talk about newborn, it
depends, so suppose
a new child is born in your family, then
you can add them from 90 years in that policy.
Similarly, if you have
children up to 15 years, then in
this policy you can cover them in
different styles.  You can keep it.
Talking about ambulance cover, friends,
I found that to be a very good thing here which is one per cent discount, maximum
Rs.10000 is
given on hospitalization. Suppose you have a
policy of Rs.1000000, then
you
get one percent ambulance cover of Rs.10,000 on every hospitalization. If you have a policy of Rs.5 lakh, then you will
get Rs.5000 cover on every hospitalization and there is
no limit on it. You
can avail this as many times as you want. Talking about pollution benefits,
friends, if you take a 2-year
plan, then you get a discount of 7.5 percent
and if you use a three-year plan, then
you get a long-term
discount of Rs.10000.
Talking about health checkup benefit, friends, that
is also very good here
that you will get 0.5% of the sum assured
and maximum Rs.10000.
If you have Rs.10 lakh, then up to Rs.5000
you can avail it.  You can avail the benefit every year.
Friends, the balance program
is also available here. There are many things in it. For example,
suppose you have undergone a diagnostic
test and have given its report or
you are not physically fit, then
this program has been designed in this way,
its deductible you will find it inside the policy website
or in the brochure. Here
you get some points and
you can redeem these points at the time of renewal. There is a
maximum discount of five percent in this.
Now there is a level, so you
can also see this, this also makes the policy quite
unique. And talking about donor expenses,
friends, this is also available here for the
time and time. If
any patient falls ill and
suppose such a situation arises that they
need kidney donation or
liver donation, then
whoever is donating here,
their entire expenses are also borne within this policy. Moving
ahead,
friends, let's talk about bariatric surgery.
So this situation happens when a person's
weight increases too much and the doctor
feels that along with the weight gain, they may have
some heart problem or some other
problem which can lead to
life threatening situations, so
for this the doctors
suggest cataract surgery, so friends, this is
customized surgery or
I can call it cosmetic surgery, it
is available here because it covers up to 50% of the time,
if you have taken a policy of 5 lakhs then it will cover you up
to Rs. 2.5 lakhs and in a policy of 10 lakhs it will
cover you up to ₹5000, the
maximum expense of this is you can bear up to ₹10
under this policy, friends,
animal white vaccination like dog
bite, monkey bite, if any
such incident happens then that is also available,
here it is up to Rs. 10000, you
can get it done, talk about the conveyance benefit under this policy,
friends, this is also
very good under this policy  The unique feature is
that suppose if anyone's hospital
stay is for more than 10 days, then the
company here will give
you a lump sum benefit of Rs 20,000,
but here it is
mandatory to have an operation of 10 days. Friends,
there is also a policy option here, you
can take the policy individually or in a futures policy.
When you come to take these 100 years,
here you cover up to nine people
in a single policy, which is
available in very few policies. Under this, you
can cover two adults, up to three children, that is, up
to three children, two parents, and parents also, that is,
one, the entire family, that is,
parents as well, and
you can get them covered under a single protection.
Talking about the relative option, friends,
here there is a lifetime guarantee, you
can renew it for a lifetime. There is no such thing in
this that you have to cover up to 90 years, 70
years, 80 years, Paul Senior, that  You
can get it done anytime.
Friends, if we talk about normal treatment, then that too is
available till Someshwar. Today I will tell you a little about
what domiciled hospitalization is. Friends, this operation is done
when the verification is not such that the person can
go to the hospital and get admitted, or even the
hospitals near you are not available. Well,
if any such situation arises
and the doctor is coming to your house and the
entire treatment is being
given like a hospital at home, then these expenses are
covered in the hospital,
provided that the duration is more than three days,
then it is
available till the end. Talking about income tax
benefits, friends, under
section active, that is also available here.
Friends, within this line, there is show by
pricing, which is very good for some people.
I will explain a little about it to you
so that you will understand it well
and you will never face any problem in it. Whatever
comes to mind, Delhi, Kolkata,
Mumbai, Thane, Pune, Hyderabad and Gujarat.
Haryana and it happened, so all these are in Zone-1,
these have been included in life because
medical expenses are charged here, okay,
and here these are charged a little more,
here you will not be
given any discount on that in Zone-2, if I talk to you
and state capitals excluding
friends, cover in which normal means all the
states we have here, okay, like let's say
Bihar, its capital is
Patna, then all the capitals
which are not available here are in Zone-1,
there those categories will be called on two,
there if you purchase this plan
and go for treatment there, then
you will get a discount of 12.5 percent,
similarly all the locations which are not in Zone-1
and are not in Zone-2,
then all those locations will
come under Zone-3 and there you will
get a discount of 15 percent in the policy, okay,
but along with this you also have to understand
that any person who has a policy of Zone-3
and he goes to Bigg Boss Zone-2 for
treatment, then he will get a discount of 1.5 percent.  You will have to
pay 12 percent, which means that if
you have purchased a policy in any city of the Union Territory
and you go for treatment in Zone 2,
within the capital of any state, then
you will have to pay 12,500 rupees from your pocket on a bill of Rs 1 lakh.
Similarly, if you
go to Zone 1 for treatment, then you will have to
pay 15 percent charge here.
Similarly, if the June Booker
price is charged on these and you go for
treatment in Zone 1, then you will have to
pay the same discount of 12.5 percent. So, I
hope
you understand this pricing, friends. If you
still don't understand it, then you can ask me
in the comments or by WhatsApping me.
I will explain it to you properly.
Moving ahead, friends, you
can also connect with me. For this, you
can follow me
on the Telegram group by the name of Insurance Sachin.
My Telegram group is here:
Insurance Sachin. You can join me from here on
Instagram.  But on Twitter and
if you have any official questions for me, you
can also ask me on email. If you
want to ask by showing any document, then you can ask.
My WhatsApp number is also available here.
27 If you like any policy,
I will tell you more about all these features later.
In this, if you like any policy very much
and you want to purchase your policy, then
you
can also purchase this policy by contacting me on this number. We
provide policy servicing all over India. So friends, let's move
ahead and start the review of this
plan and talk about Ad Observer in it.
Friends, this advance cover
also makes this plan the most unique
because you can add any ad you want in it according to
your requirement. So
now let's talk
friends about maternity cover. The
maternity cover here is very good. The
waiting period here is only 9 months,
but you will have to purchase this plan for 3 years together.  The
pricing of the maternity cover will be added here
as well as if suppose you have
bought a plan of Rs 10 lakh here, then
you will get ten percent of it i.e. Rs 1 lakh as
matriculation and you will keep getting it every
year so if you have bought a 3 year
plan here then the Prince Charles plan of 3 years will be
matriculation three
degrees i.e. till the birth of three children,
you will be given coverage of Rs 1 lakh and
you have bought a policy of Rs 10 lakh here
and this coverage can go up to a maximum of Rs 10 lakh
so friends if you want to
see medium pressure inside this plan then you will have to buy a 3 year
airplane together as well as
suppose you have
also selected newborn baby cover here which is Don,
Don means that you will have to pay
separate money for each option, so
whatever your newborn baby cover is here
you will get it but how will you get it,
double the price of whatever maternity cover will be there, that is suppose
in this case someone has taken a loan from his father's
10 lakhs  If you have purchased a policy, its
10% is ₹1, so
how much cover will you get for the child here, 2 lakh rupees,
or suppose any child is
born and some problem arises with him, he has to be
kept in the nursery, there is a
need for care and there
you also know that there are very high charges as per the
elders, so you will get
cover up to 2 lakh rupees for the new born baby here, the option of
vaccination for newborn baby
is also available here, friends, in this there is one per
cent of chilli and that means if you have
taken a loan of 10 lakhs, then you will get
10000 rupees here, the maximum age
limit is 10,000 rupees for up to one year old child, that is,
whatever vaccination you have for one year,
some are for 2000, some for
eye, some for 4000, so by activating in this way,
why is it up to rs. 10000, you
can take cover for newborn vaccination here, so OPD and here I will talk about
OPD very  Whatever people need,
it is available here. Okay,
in medical and dental, dental treatment is
not covered by Muslim policies and
medical does not do OPD either, so both of those are
available here. In this, you are given a compensation of 0.5%, maximum up
to Rs 1 lakh, that is,
0.5% of whatever you have taken, your OPD limit will be
reduced. There are network
hospitals here, you can link to their network
of doctors, now you
can get your treatment here and get the bill
debited from the company. Friends,
sometimes what happens is that there are some changes in the plane, I
cannot change them in the match video, so
whenever you go to any line, you
must go to the description and see whatever
details there are in the description under the change plan. Let's
talk about personal accidents, friends,
so its addition is also available
here, that if a mother dies due to an accident, then you will get whatever amount of
compensation you have chosen.
You will get it covered under Permanent Total Disability, that is,
Partial Permanent
Disability is covered here and
in this you can see a maximum of ₹5000000,
for this friends you will have to pay a little
extra money and this
personal accident coverage will also be
assigned in your policy,
talking about domestic air ambulance
friends, if many people feel that I may
need this ambulance, I
need this ambulance, then for that also you
can spare your time here, the limit is available, you just type
Sector-65 here, purchase this admin
and you will get this limit, let's move
ahead friends, let's talk about Hospital Delhi
Cantt, it also makes this initiative
quite unique, it is
not available in many areas, but you
can get hospital here from ₹500 to ₹25000, for example,
₹500 thousand rupees, ₹2000  ₹5000 in this way,
which is what you can take according to your budget,
you will not only be given the cost of treatment but also the
telecast amount will be
transferred to your bank account
because you had made this purchase.
Talking about critical illness cover,
friends, there are 20 such serious diseases
for which you can purchase this plan
if any of these diseases
is requested and suppose you had taken constipation and 5 lakhs or 10
lakhs, then as soon as that
disease is detected,
5 lakhs and 10 lakh rupees will be deposited in your bank account. In the
end, the tehsil will pay the expenses,
it will be over and above so that you
can manage your household expenses, raise your children,
if you have a loan, then you
can pay it. This is a
critical illness, if you want to know its details then
you can contact me and ask. Let's move ahead
friends, I
told you in the beginning of the line that this is a very
customizable plan, a very good
plan.  Let me tell you
how you can reduce your premium here,
how you can choose things according to your needs,
what are the two best things in this,
speed i.e. pre-existing, which we
call, its waiting period
is inbuilt in the plan of 2 years, if
you want to take the plan after 3 years, then the waiting period will be
reduced a bit, if you want to take the plan for 4 years, then
your premium will be reduced,
suppose you do not have the pre-existing plan, then
you can use the 4 year plan
because your premium is not applicable in it, then
your premium will be reduced further,
special division friends, here the
waiting period which the company has mentioned is of
2 years, if you want to make it one
year, then that option
is also available, here it will
increase a little bit, but like cataract,
hernia, joint replacement or
entry related disorders or uterus
removal, stones, all these are covered after about 2 years in every plan,
yes also after 2 years  It
happens but if you want to
cover it after this year then you
can get it done there, in this you can see a little bit of yours in the film,
friends here I
told you about its six days and add, if
you want that I do
not need it much, even 3460 is enough for me then
now you can choose here, this will
reduce your payment a little more, so see
this is a very customizable plan for you
friends, one payment option
is available here which I would suggest you
never to take, but still you have the option,
so let me tell you that there are many people who
say that whatever the plan
bill comes, we will pay 10 percent or 20 percent of it,
but we
want a low premium, so that option is also available here,
suppose an Ola bill comes, you have
cleared the 10 percent payment here,
then you will have to pay Rs 20000 from your pocket
voluntarily and the rest will be paid by the
company, by taking this option
your premium will be reduced, but I
always tell you this  I will suggest which one to adopt.
Okay, and here this is done
only on the request of the customer care helpline.
Now let's talk friends,
explain that although I have already
told you about it, but still I will
explain a little more to you that
in plain language, the waiting period for the test
digit is 3 years, you
can customize it by 4 years. Friends, there
is a waiting period here, like for cataract,
hernia, joint replacement, you
can reduce it to one year. There is a 30-day
meeting, friends, which is done in all the wards, in this
you are given accident cover only
within the first 30 days, only
after that any disease after 30 days
is covered. There is a waiting period of 9 months for
maternity cover. Friends, I
want to tell you a little more
about the maternity cover. There is a
very good thing in the slide, you should understand it carefully,
suppose you bought a policy for maternity cover
and you paid for three years' coverage
together, but you did not pay for these
three  If you are not able to plan your baby within a year, then
you will feel that all your
Prevent has gone to waste, but the company has
inbuilt a very good thing in it, that if suppose you have
taken a three-year plan, you have
not planned your maternity, but you want to
blend the maternity in the next three years, then you can still blend it, then
what will happen here is that if you have
not taken any plan, then all your Mathematica Prevent plans for the next three years will be done, that is, the
3-year
policy that you had bought, your coverage for the next three years and
maternity will be done, and the
companies will not charge you any premium,
so friends, I found this to be a
very good plan, and along with this, there is
loot from ICU, which is
also a very strong brand, so I hope
that you have understood it, friends,
if you have understood it, then do
not forget to share this video with your friends, if you are new to my channel, then do
not forget to subscribe to it because
I will bring such videos for you.  I keep coming
and will keep bringing it in the future as well, so friends,
I will meet you in the next video, my
name is Sachin Verma, thank you very much for watching this video.